# PROFILES

Website: kuldippatel.dev

**LinkedIn:** linkedin.com/in/kp7742 **GitHub:** github.com/kp7742 **Twitter:** twitter.com/kexecv

# EDUCATION

JUN 2013 - MAR 2014

### 10th Board

R.S.M. Poonawala Sarvajanik Experimental School, Surat, Gujarat, India

JUN 2015 - MAR 2016

### 12th Board

R.S.M. Poonawala Sarvajanik Experimental School, Surat, Gujarat, India

AUG 2016 - PRESENT

### **B.E** in Computer Engineering

R.N.G. Patel Institute of Technology, Bardoli, Gujarat, India

## SKILLS

C/C++		
JAVA		
Python		
РНР		
JavaScript		
HTML / CSS		
	l	

## CERTIFICATION

"Google Cloud Platform: Core Infrastructure" Coursera | Mar 2019

"Software Engineering – IT Services"
Aspiring Minds | Sep 2019

# KULDIP PATEL

Phone: +91 9998897742 | Email: patel.kuldip91@gmail.com

Address: 33-1/109, Near Ambika Niketan Temple, Parle Point, Surat, Gujarat

### ABOUT ME

I'm 21 years old and I'm a Computer Orchestrate by Profession and also, I'm Intermediate Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the Android apps and Websites. Skilled in C++, Java, PHP, Android and Cyber Security. Currently pursuing my Bachelor Degree in RNGPIT College, Surat

# EXPERIENCE

SEP 2019

### Lead Backend Developer | Visvesmruti 2019

RNGPIT - Gujarat - India

MAR 2019 - OCT 2019

### Student Partner | Internshala

RNGPIT - Gujarat - India

JAN 2019 - AUG 2020

### Developer Student Club Community Lead | DSC RNGPIT

RNGPIT - Gujarat - India

# PROJECTS

"AIKYAM" | Etherium + BlockChain | Feb 2020 Blockchain Based Unique Person Identification System At DotSlash 3.0 Hackathon

"TOBA" | Website + Android App | Mar 2019
Token Based Authentication System for Industry 4.0 Conference

"<u>VSManage</u>" | Website + Android App | Sep 2019 Management System for Technical Festival At Visvesmruti 2019

"<u>WAAutoResponder</u>" | Android App | May 2019 Whatsapp Chat Auto Reply Bot for Automation As Side Project.

"SathChalein" | Android App | Feb 2019

Android App to Bridge gap Between Two Parties for Sharing Trips At DotSlash 2.0

"Visvesmruti App" | Android App | Sep 2018

Official Application For Technical Festival At Visvesmruti 2018, RNGPIT College

"KnowYourCampus" | Android App | Feb 2018

Android App for College Work, TimeTable, Assignment At DotSlash 1.0 Hackathon